Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
So this is an Alabasta city.
Is there food?
Listen carefully, guys.
I want you all to do your best to
control yourselves while we're here.
Of course, Nami.
You do realize the one
who needs to hear that
warning the most has
already abandoned ship.
He doesn't know the meaning of control.
What now?
He's easy to find.
Just look for the area with the commotion.
That's where he'll be.
He's right.
I wish he'd at least remember that he
has a bounty on that rubbery head of his.
Especially while we're
in a big country like.
Forget about Luffy.
He could take care of himself.
Now let's go find some food.
We can get to work after that.
They're all?
this safe.
What's wrong, Karoo? Mr. Three's ship!
I thought we took care of
that creep for good already.
I'm certain it's him.
That ship couldn't even run without Mr.
Three's wax, wax, fruit powers.
The bastard's here.
This isn't good.
Hey, what happened?
What's everybody looking at?
I said some guy just dropped
dead sitting up at the counter.
The food's never been that bad before.
What's going on?
What happened?
Well, someone died.
Apparently, he suddenly dropped dead
right in the middle of the restaurant.
He just died?
Yeah, he just up and keeled over
during a conversation with the owner.
He isn't from here.
We think he may have accidentally eaten
a desert strawberry while traveling,
not knowing what it was.
Uh, what is a desert strawberry?
There's a species of
poisonous spiders that
look like red strawberries
growing in the desert.
Anyone who eats one will
suddenly die a few days later.
The infection spreads throughout
the corpse and it's contagious,
so no one can go near.
It's a quick but unpleasant way to go.
You have to be careful in the desert.
Anything you touch can kill you.
But just look at the way his
arm is still stuck up like that,
holding on to a bite of meat.
That's proof of just how swiftly
the desert strawberry acts.
Let me see.
It's an incredibly deadly creature.
I can't believe I can burn this.
I came back to life!
Um are you all right
Sorry about that fell asleep You were
asleep that doesn't make
sense You were right
in the middle of a conversation And now
you're just eating like nothing happened
Jeez what's all the commotion about
anyway We thought you had dropped out
are you crazy Does this restaurant of
yours do comedy skits or something?
Nope, that isn't our thing. Not here.
We're just glad that you're alright.
Damn it! Cut it out!
Yeah, I think that ought to do it.
Tell me, mister.
What is it?
Have you by any chance seen this guy?
He's a pirate that wears a Straw Hat.
You've got some nerve eating in the
middle of a public place like this.
Even for division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
Hello, Portgas D. Ace.
Huh? No way!
Not the Whitebeard Pirates!
I knew I'd seen that
mark on his back before.
You mean this weirdo is one
of the white-beard pirates?
It's the mark of the white-beard
pirates, but what is he doing here?
I'm curious.
What's such a big-shot
pirate doing in this country?
I'm looking for someone.
My little brother.
Give me food!
What's with this weirdo city anyway?
There's some strange non-food
smell all over the place!
There's one!
It's a restaurant!
So, what do you want from me now, Captain?
I'd just like you to come
with me quietly. No thanks.
I think I'll pass.
Yeah, figured you'd say that.
I'm here in Alabasta trying to hunt down
another pirate at the moment to be honest.
I have no real interest in capturing you
right now then just look the other way.
I'm afraid I can't do
that not as long as I'm a
marine and you're part of
a notorious pirate crew.
That's not much of a reason now is?.
How about I give you one.
I'm going to rock it!
Woo! Food!
Now I can eat!
Finally, I'm starving!
I thought I was gonna die!
Old guy, give me food.
Hurry, come on.
Food, food, food, food!
No, no, no!
Wow, this is beautiful!
Oh yeah, love it!
Well, I know I asked you to
pick out some clothes for us,
but these were meant for dancer girls.
Oh, Vivi!
You're a fission!
But commoners wouldn't wear this.
But aren't dancers common?
We're crossing a desert!
Hey, don't worry!
If you get tired, my
darling, I'll just carry you!
This is pointless.
Now then, let's take a look at you guys.
Compared to the lovely ladies,
you two look like sloppy bandits.
You might want to look in a mirror.
Hey, Chopper, what are you doing?
It's a smell.
Oh, yeah, where did you run off to?
Just somewhere.
Is he not feeling well?
Yeah, it's just the perfume.
Chopper can't stand it.
Perfume?
Oh, yeah, Tony has an
incredibly sensitive nose.
This stuff?
Some of it does have
a really strong smell.
You smell just like an angel
in a field of fresh flowers.
You're an idiot.
At any rate,
at least we've managed to
gather all the supplies
that we're going to need
to cross the desert?
Yeah, this oasis, you said
it's called Yuba, right?
Yes, that's correct, but first we'll
have to travel through the desert
Amazing!
This is seriously the
best food I've ever tasted
Uh, yes, thanks a lot, but you see, sir
It's just, well, you might
want to start running now.
What is that?
Damn it.
So what the hell was that?
What just happened?
This is ridiculous.
Just look at this place.
Oh, hi there.
Many apologies for disturbing your meal.
What kind of world-class idiot
would do something like this?
Hey, Luke!
Straw Hat!
I've been looking for you Straw Hat.
I thought you'd be here seems.
I was correct
Would you quit eating
Oh, you're that smoky guy,
what are you doing in Alabasta?
Wait a sec.
Thanks a lot for the meal.
Now stop you!
Wait up, Luffy, it's me!
Hold on a second, hey!
Come back, Luffy!
I didn't pay.
This is bad.
My Gum-Gum moves don't work
against this guy at all!
I just have to make a run for it now.
Yes, sir.
Would you like a cool towel?
It's quite refreshing.
This desert kingdom really is hot.
Catch that guy It's Straw Hat! Yes, sir!
I've got him!
Tajiki, gather the marines at once!
Search every inch of this
place for the rest of his crew!
Right!
Come on!
They must have double
fruit powers. No way!
The Straw Hat's crew is here.
That must mean...
Roronoa Zoro is in the city somewhere.
White snake!
Where could Luffy have gone?
He doesn't know the island at all.
Seriously, a crew shouldn't have to work
this hard to keep track of their captain.
Oh, Nami!
This doesn't look good.
We could be in some serious trouble
if we don't get out of here soon.
Trouble?
Why's that?
Because the Marines are here.
Marines?
Let's just find Luffy as fast as possible
and get out of this
town as soon as we can.
Hey, Tide! What for?
What was that?
It's the Marines.
Yeah, and they're excited about something.
Don't let that pirate escape after him!
I'm sure it's nothing.
They're probably chasing some idiot
pirate who's running crazy around town.
It's Ote!
Oh, hey, Zoro!
Oh, so that's where you guys have been!
No, you morons!
Get rid of them first!
Well, they're coming.
What should we do now?
We've gotta get going.
To the ship!
Don't just stand there, we gotta go!
Wait up!
Stop right there, pirates!
You can fall back now, men.
Captain, that straw had a spine to
finish. Not good! Here it comes! What?
Not good!
Not good! Eat hay!
You again.
Just give it up.
While you may have the power
of smoke, mine is fire.
A fight between the two
of us would be pointless.
It would probably go on forever.
All right.
Looks like the Mystery Man
has devil for his powers.
Who is this guy anyway?
That you, Ace?
You haven't changed a bit,
Luffy. It is you. Really?
Wow, did you eat a devil
fruit or something?
Yeah, the flame flame fruit.
We'll secure the
perimeter, Captain Smoker.
Anyway, now's probably
not the time for chatting.
You guys get out of here.
I'll catch up.
Don't worry about these guys.
I've got them.
Go on. Let's go!
Yeah, coming!
But Luffy...
Who is that guy back there?
How did he do that?
Boy, spark!
A fire!
That's no ordinary fire.
What's going on back there?
Looks like a fight between smoke and fire.
So that's the kind of power you get
after eating a flame flame fruit.
Speaking of Devil Fruit,
Luffy, is it true?
Is that guy really your brother?
Yep, his name's Ace.
Look, I'm not surprised to
hear you have a brother, Luffy.
But what's he doing
here on the Grand Line?
Ace is a pirate too, just like I am.
He left home three years before I
did to go search for the One Piece.
Anyway, he bought us some
time, so we can't waste it.
Let's get back to the ship.
Sure, Nami, dear.
Wow, I never would have thought I'd run
into my big brother in a place like this.
Ah!
Which way do we go?
Left, Doosop, everyone get that?
Yes, Nami, I'll follow
you wherever you go.
You close, sick freak. Whoa!
A fight between flame and
smoke is ultimately pointless,
as we've just made obvious.
Where's the Straw Hat and his crew?
They're gone, sir. So is Ace.
We've lost sight of him.
I run into the Straw Hat in the Grand
Line and have him as good as captured.
But then, you just had to get
in my way, didn't you, Ace?
Get everything stowed!
We're shoving off right away!
Aye, aye!
Set the sails!
But it took us so long
to finally get here.
And now we're leaving already, BB?
Yes, but remember,
we only stopped here to
get the supplies we're
going to need for the rest of the journey.
And now that we have all of them,
we're going to head upriver
into the interior of Alabasta.
Our next destination is the
City of Green, Aramaloo.
Aramaloo? Hurry! I am!
Pick up the pace!
Ready!
Right! Set sail!
Huh?
Ah, damn it.
You know, I have the strangest
feeling we're forgetting something.
What the?
Oh, well, that's weird.
I could have sworn they were right here.
But now they're all gone.
Where'd they go?
Well, I guess giving you a
chance to escape was pointless.
Hey!
Hiya, Ace.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You can say that.
How many years has it been?
I don't know, but you haven't
changed much over that time.
You're a little taller, but
you pretty much look the same.
So do you.
Aside from those powers you got
from eating that Devil Fruit,
you haven't changed a bit.
Remember when you used to sneak into
the fields, eat a hundred watermelons,
spit the seeds out like a
gatling gun and run away?
No, that wasn't me.
That was you.
The farmers would chase you
and you'd scream like a girl.
That was you too.
I watched and laughed.
Guess we're still the same sure are
Just like old times wait wasn't your crew
looking for you a few minutes ago. Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing in this country?
Anyway, I take it.
You never received the message.
I left for you back on drum Island
Well, I guess that's
a no, but don't worry.
It's no big deal It was just to let you
know that I'd be an
Alabasta for a few days.
I'm in these waters on
some business Business huh?
Yeah I'm with the White Beard Pirates.
Catch the White Beard Pirates.
See this tattoo?
That's our mark and it's my pride.
So Luffy, why don't you and your
friends come join us? Come on!
It'll be fun.
What do you say?
No thanks.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
That's too bad because?
But you see, Whitebeard's the
greatest pirate I've ever met.
That's why I'm going to help
him become King of the Pirates.
And not you, Luffy. Sorry.
That's fine.
I guess we'll just have to fight then.
Because I'm going to
be King of the Pirates.
Stop it!
Don't drink at all, you mooch!
Hey!
Something big must be going on in town.
All the Marines on board
wouldn't have left me
and the ship unattended
like this if there wasn't.
Oh, well, whatever it is, it's given
me a perfect opportunity to escape.
Mr. Eleven.
Well, now, since you know my codename,
that can only mean that the three
of you are members of Baroque Works.
I'd guess millions.
Hurry up and untie me.
You're right about one thing.
We're with Baroque Works.
But we're in line to become
number agents, you see.
We're not millions, we're billions.
You are a numbered agent, but looks
like you're barely one at that.
A stronger agent would have never been
captured by the Marines like this.
Can we discuss this later?
Like when I'm not tied up, maybe?
Now help another member out before
all those Marines come back.
Oh, we'll help you, all right.
Right off this mortal coil, that is.
A billions can get promoted to a numbered
agent whenever there's a seat to fill.
And your position is about to be empty.
WAIT! NO! HOLD ON!
HEY!
You won't believe it!
Firefist Ace is here! What?
Firefist Ace?
You mean the second division
commander of the Whitebeard Pirates?
If we can take someone
with his reputation down,
then we're guaranteed
to become number agents.
Here we are You see your ship?
You can't escape from us.
Oh, there it is.
Hey, over here, you guys!
We're here.
Luffy, you go on ahead
and now you already went.
Oh, I don't believe it!
I found Luffy.
Are you sure?
Yeah, that stupid mug is
definitely his. Uh-oh?
Hey, guys!
Lanchi! Tony!
Are you all right?
Oh, Luffy came back!
Yeah, the hard way.
Sorry about that, guys.
My bad.
Yeah, you're sorry, all right.
The sorryest excuse for a captain
who's ever sailed the sea, you moron!
Do you have any idea how much
trouble you've put us in?
Can't you at least try and
act like a captain sometime?
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's right. Where's Ace? Ace?
You're with your brother, huh?
Wait a minute.
You didn't just leave him, did you?
Um, sort of, but don't worry.
Ace is really strong.
So how strong is he?
Well, let me put it like this.
When we were younger, I was never
able to beat him in a fight,
and this was way back in the days
before he ate a flame flame fruit.
That's how strong my big brother is.
You mean there's a flesh-and-blood
person that you couldn't beat?
The big brother of a monster
is an even bigger monster.
I guess so, because Ace used
to beat me up all the time.
But I bet now I can kick his big butt.
I'd like to see you try
and back that claim up.
So, exactly whose butt's getting kicked?
Oh, hey, Ace.
This is my crew I was telling you about.
Nice to meet you, and thanks for
taking care of my kid brother.
I know he's a handful.
Oh, no, not at all.
Come on, be honest.
This is Luffy we're talking about.
Isn't he a bit much for
you to handle at times?
Not at all.
You're good people.
Well, sit down and relax.
I'm sure you two have
lots of catching up to do.
I'll make some tea.
No, that's thoughtful, but
I don't want to impose.
It's not exactly what I expected.
I'll say.
He's polite, helpful, and gracious,
the polar opposite of Luffy.
One of them only cares
about stuffing his face.
There's no way these two can be brothers.
Well, the other only
cares about his brother.
I wish I had a wonderful
brother like that.
Brother, I wish I had a
wonderful captain like that.
Saatchi, he's kidding.
See, I told you they were interesting.
Baroque Works, those
are the Billions ships.
Are we going to let them
escape from the Billions?
No way!
Hey, we'll show him what Baroque works
billions are made of, full speed ahead!
Those guys again?
Luffy, leave it to me, I'll handle it.
He's going all by himself?
And in that dinky bow, too.
I wouldn't worry about him if I were you.
They don't let just
anyone become the second
division commander of
the Whitebeard Pirates.
Is he insane?
Firefest is heading right towards us.
Let him come!
Our ships are going to make
matchsticks out of his.
He jumped!
Open fire!
Throw him to pieces, men!
Fire fist!
He roasted them!
Captain Smoker,
we've combed the entire city, sir,
but Straw Hat Luffy and his
crew are nowhere to be found.
Do you want to know who I saw with them?
Vivi, and I'm certain it was her, too.
Vivi?
As in Princess Vivi Nefertari?
But what would she be doing
with the Straw Hat pirates?
She must be their hostage.
They probably abducted her in the hopes
that her father would pay a hefty ransom.
Doubt it.
She wasn't acting like a kidnapped
victim, more like part of the crew.
The princess acting like a pirate?
Something strange is happening.
I just wish I knew what it was.
Captain Smoker!
I'm sorry, sir, but it appears that Mr.
Eleven was killed on board the ship while
we were off searching for the Straw Hats,
who, by the way, we still
haven't located yet.
Call off the search for Straw Hat Luffy.
I have a pretty good
idea where he's headed.
He's after Crocodile. I'm sure of it.
Why Crocodile?
He's one of the seven warlords of the sea.
A pirate given government approval.
I find all of the seven warlords despicable,
but Crocodile's the absolute worst.
Politically speaking, isn't he an ally
of the world government and the Marines?
Crocodile might have the powers
that be fooled, but not me.
They're delusional if they think giving
him a sanction will make him obey.
He's a pirate.
There's one thing you always
need to remember, Tashigi.
A pirate's a pirate no
matter where they go.
They never change.
Crocodile will lead us right to him.
Straw Hat will show up wherever he is.
And I'm sure we'll find out
what's going on when we get there.
There'll be no escape
for him. Not this time.
Woo-hoo!
Time to celebrate, guys!
She's one of us now!
Here's the Fire Fist Ace!
Cheers!
Wait, who said I was joining your crew?
And to delicious drinks oh don't worry
anything they say seriously when they're
like this they Get all
goofy when they drink
you sure you don't
want to join us it'll
be fun I promise I can't right Now I'm
chasing someone now he's a pirate named
blackbeard blackbeard we've heard of him
he was the one who attacked Drum Kingdom.
You see,
Blackbeard used to be a member of the
Second Division of the Whitebeard Pirates.
He was one of my own men, but he committed
the most unforgivable sin a pirate!
could.
He killed one of his fellow crew
members, and then he jumped ship.
As commander of his division, it's my
responsibility to take care. of him.
So that's why you're after him.
We've just entered the Sandora River.
We'll take it to Aramalu,
where we'll dock?
and then we'll proceed on foot
until we reach Yuba, here.
The leader of the rebel army is there.
That's where we're going.
You don't say.
Do you mind if I tag along?
Mommy, Vivi, I'll follow you anywhere.
Just tell me where to go.
Hopefully it's off of a cliff.
What did you say, Saru?
Cool it, you two.
Well, looks like you'll be with
us for a little while, Ace.
We're all really happy to have you aboard.
This is going to be fun to Ace.
Cheers!
You